question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first "
                    "publisher, Sun Tzu.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The 'Squaring the Circle' problem is solvable.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The binary number '101001101' is equivalent to the Decimal number '334'",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A 'Millinillion' is a real number.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number 'i'.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60Â°.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
